dcons.com 2002-10-17

# Privacy Policy

Datacons Private Limited recognises privacy and security as being a concern for most individuals accessing the Internet. Whether you're buying one of our quality products, or just browsing our site, we want to make you comfortable with our privacy policy and the security measures we take to protect your personal information. The following policy will give you a better understanding of what we do towards security: 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

  * This Privacy Policy covers Datacons Private Limited treatment of personally identifiable information that Datacons collects when you are on the Datacons site, and when you use Datacons services. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Datacons does not own or control, or to people that Datacons does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and/or to administer our Web site. This gives us an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a users session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by www.dcons.com as set forth in the policy currently in effect. If we decide to change our policy, such changes will be posted here on the Web site, so please check back periodically to ensure you have the most current policy. 

**Cookies**  
www.dcons.com may set and access www.dcons.com cookies on your computer. Cookies are generally used for tracking certain traffic patterns. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services or engage in activities that require registration in order to participate.

**How is my Information used?**  
Our site's registration form may require you to give us contact information like your name and e-mail address. We use this contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company. 

**With whom is my information shared?**  
Datacons never provides your personal information to third-parties without your consent. Datacons may share the information you provide with its subsidiaries and related companies. 

**Security measures to protect the information collected.**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of information under our control. This security measure helps ensure that no impostors, eavesdroppers, or vandals get your personal information. 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at every point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site may contain links to other sites. **Datacons Private Ltd.** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [datacons@dcons.com](mailto:datacons@dcons.com)
